OK, so now, we're hitting a ball.
The wind is blowing from right to left, which means, it's just blowing from this direction, to that direction.
And how do we deal with that?
Well, if I hit this ball straight down the middle of the fairway, and the wind is going from right to left, it's going to blow it possibly into the left side of the fair way, or the left rough.
Or if it's a real strong wind, it could blow it into the out of bounds on the left side.
So, I have to adjust and account for that wind, so, what I'm going to do is there's a variety of things I can do.
So I'm using my five iron here.
I could then play a thade, which means the ball is going to curl, it's going to curl into the wind, and then the wind is going to straighten it back out.
And I'm going to move some distance doing that, but that's one way of avoiding the ball from being pushed all the way to the left side.
Another thing I could do is aim more to the right, and I can hit the ball straight, and then, so if I hit the ball more to the right, the wind is going to push it right back into the middle, I hope.
or, I could aim very far to the right, and use a draw, which is kind of an easy hook, so I aim really far to the right, and now by hitting a draw I'm going to get a little more distance, so then I count, so that counteracts the wind, the distance robbing wind.
So if I hit it really far to the right, the wind is going to then push it, and I might be somewhat on the right side of the fairway.
So those are the ways you deal with the right to left wind.
So, if I'm going to fade the ball, I'm going to aim to the right side, like that.
And then the wind will correct it, hopefully, down the middle.
And, but I might want to draw it and then really go right, so I'm going to close the face a little bit.
And then the wind is going to blow that right down the middle.
So what you don't want to do when you have a really strong right to left wind is go down the middle or even play near the left side, because the wind can push you out of bounds, or into a lot rough and trees.